少喝点
范总敬你一个
好好好嗯
够了范总
我也敬你一个啊
那好好好
来干了
好好事成双
咱再来一杯
你们慢慢喝
我去趟洗手间啊
范总我跟你一块去嗯
各位我是范总的秘书
范总身体爆样
我来带他喝
好好啊
女中豪杰好酒量
苏秘书好酒量哎
范总喝不了了
你得陪我们多喝几杯啊
你什么意思啊
你是瞧不起我老唐是吗
Drink less
Mr. Fan respects you
Ok ok ok
Enough, Mr. Fan
I respect you too.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on
Good things come in pairs
Let's have another drink
You drink slowly
I'm going to the bathroom
Mr. Fan, I'll go with you
Ladies and gentlemen, I am Mr. Fan's secretary
Mr. Fan's body exploded
I'll bring him a drink
Okay, okay.
The heroic woman has a good appetite for alcohol
Secretary Su is a good drinker
Mr. Fan can't drink anymore
Do you need to accompany us for a few more drinks?
What do you mean?
Are you looking down on my old Tang?